http://www.zell-metall.com/en/infocenter/privacy-statement

This website uses cookies to improve user-friendliness, web analysis, and social media integration. Click on "Accept all cookies" or assign your own indivdual settings. All information about data protection is available unter data protection.
Accept all cookies
Individual settings
This provides you an overview of all the cookies used and allows you to make individual settings. All details can be found under data protection.
Essential
Essential cookies enable basic website functions. The website cannot function properly without them.
DETAILS
Cookie-Name
Type
Expiry
eZSESSID
Session
is_logged_in
HTTP
Marketing/Statistics
Statistics cookies are used to anonymously gather data in order to improve the user-friendliness on the website. Marketing cookies are used by third parties or publishers in order to display personalized advertising.
DETAILS
Google Analytics
Cookie-Name
Type
Expiry
__utma
HTTP
2 Years
External media
Content from external media is blocked as standard. If cookies from external media are accepted, access to external content no longer reqiures manual consent.
DETAILS
YouTube
Cookie-Name
Type
Expiry
GPS
HTTP
1 Day
PRIVACY STATEMENT
We are delighted that you are visiting our website and thank you for your interest in our company and our products and services. It is important to us to make sure that your personal data is protected while you are using our website. We will therefore process your data exclusively in accordance with legal provisions. This Privacy Statement sets out the main aspects of data processing on our website. By continuing to use our website, you agree that your data may be processed in accordance with this Privacy Statement.
1) CONTACTING US
In principle, you may visit our website without us collecting any personal data from you. Personal data will only be collected if you provide it to us voluntarily by contacting us. If you make contact with us using a form on the website or by email, the data you provide will only be used, without your explicit consent, for the purpose of handling your enquiries and will be stored by us for six months to deal with any follow-up queries. We will not pass this data on to third parties without your consent.
2) OUR SERVICES
We will collect personal data if you register for the material comparison or product finder services on our website. In order to execute these services or the transactions requested by you, we will store the following data: email address, name, address and telephone / mobile phone number. We will pass your personal data on to affiliated companies or other companies within the Klepsch Group if this is necessary in order to execute the services you desire or to provide the information you have requested.
3) NEWSLETTER
In addition, personal data will be collected if you subscribe to our email newsletter. For this purpose we will require your email address, language and your declaration that you have agreed to receive the newsletter. We will use this data for our own advertising purposes in the form of our email newsletter provided that you have explicitly consented to this. Once you have subscribed to the newsletter, we will send you a confirmation email containing a link to confirm your subscription.You can cancel the newsletter at any time via the designated link in the newsletter or by sending a corresponding message to the email address datenschutz@zmk.at
. Once you have unsubscribed, your email address will be deleted immediately.
4) WEBSHOP
We point out, that for the purpose of simpler ordering process and for the following processing of contracts, the IP data of the connection owner are stored in the context of cookies by the web shop operator, as well as company name, email address, name, address, telephone number and fax number of the buyer. The user accounts remain until the user deletes the account. Contract data will be processed until the limitation of possible post-contractual obligations. There is no legal or contractual obligation to provide personal data. However, the provision is required to conclude the contract. The non-provision means that no contract can be concluded. A data transfer to third parties does not take place.
5) COOKIES
In order to make a visit to our website more appealing and more user-friendly, and to enable the use of certain features, we use “cookies” on various pages. Cookies are small text files that will be stored on your terminal. Some of the cookies we use (“session cookies”) will be deleted again after the browser session ends, i.e. after you close your browser. Other cookies will remain on your terminal and will enable us or other companies within the Klepsch Group to recognise your browser on your next visit (“persistent cookies”). You can set your browser so that it informs you about the installation of cookies so you can decide on an individual basis whether to accept them or you can set your browser not to accept any cookies at all or only to accept them for certain cases. If you do not accept cookies, this may restrict the functionality of our website.
6) WEB ANALYTICS SERVICE
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer to help the website analyse how you use the site, among other things. As a rule, the information generated by the cookie about your use of this website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on a server in the USA.
However, if IP anonymisation is activated on this website, your IP address will be truncated by Google within the Member States of the European Union or in other countries that are signatories of the treaty on the European Economic Area beforehand. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be sent to a Google server in the USA to be truncated there. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to analyse your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide other services associated with the use of this website and the internet in general for the website operator.The IP address sent by your browser/terminal when using Google Analytics will not be combined with any other Google data. You may prevent the storage of cookies through a corresponding setting in your browser software; please note, however, that in this case not all the features of this website may be fully available to you. In addition, you can prevent the collection of the data generated by the cookie relating to your use of the website (incl. your IP address) for Google as well as the processing of such data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plugin available via the following link: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en Please note that this website uses Google Analytics with the extension “_anonymizeIp()” and therefore IP addresses are only processed further in a truncated form to prevent them from being traced directly to a specific person.
Anonymized data will be also compiled and processed for analysis through services provided by LeadingReports GmbH (leadingreports.de) and Lead Lab GmbH (www.wiredminds.de
) (to progressively improve our website and our products. This is done by using cookies or local- and session-storage. By means of the analysis of this gathered information it is possible for to visualize the user behavior on the pages of . This visualization is focused particularly on analyzing different fields of interest by evaluating the usage of the respective webpages and the geographic origin of users. This compiled data will be processed and provided exclusively to and will not be passed to third parties beyond . Likewise this data will never be used for other purposes or even be sold. The servers used to analyze this data are operating exclusively in sovereign territory of the Federal Republic of Germany. The delivery of the services of LeadingReports GmbH and Lead Lab GmbH for underlie the german and european data privacy laws and their internationally accredited high standards. If you do not agree with the analysis of your anonymized data, click on the following link to object to the use of your data. Keep in mind that this objection will be saved using cookies or local-storage-entries to prevent the analysis of your userdata. If you delete your browser-cookies or use another browser for your next visit, this link has to be clicked again to prevent the usage of your data. As far as IP-addresses are gathered, those will be anonymized immediately after collection by deleting the last block of digits. A permanent denial of gathering and saving data by LeadingReports GmbH can be achieved at io.leadingreports.de/exclude-ip (https://io.leadingreports.de/exclude-ip
).
7) YOUR RIGHTS AND HOW TO CONTACT US
You have a right of access to your stored data free of charge as well as a right to rectification, to erasure, to restriction of processing and to portability of such data. You also have a right to appeal to the Austrian Data Protection Authority (Wickenburggasse 8, 1080 Wien, dsb@dsb.gv.at
). This website is maintained by Zell-Metall Gesellschaft m.b.H. Please contact us if you have any further questions regarding the collection, processing or use of your personal data, or if you wish to access, block, erase and rectify your personal data or revoke your consent. Our contact address is as follows:
Zell-Metall Gesellschaft m.b.H.
Privacy
Attn: Data Protection Coordinator
Schulstraße 16, A-5710 Kaprun
datenschutz@zellamid.com
Exclude from tracking.
